AIDEN CHUBET

(860)384-3871 | AChubet14@gmail.com | Southington, CT

Summary

Seasoned Network/Cloud Administrator with 7-year background in Information Technology. Accomplished in designing solutions to achieve network and software compatibility, as well as, streamlining system upgrades. After 4 years managing environments in the United States Navy and 3 years in the private sector, I have developed a love for all laas, Paas, Saas, and IaC environmental options. Career achievements in large-scale software deployments, network buildouts, system/task automation, compliance and more while utilizing Windows, Linux, MacOS, Azure, AWS, Docker, Terraform, etc.

Active Secret Security Clearance and Top Secret/SCI eligible.

GitHub: https://github.com/Aiden-Chubet

Experience

Community Mental Health Affiliates | New Britain, CT Network/Cloud Administrator | 09/2022 - Present

- **Automation** Created PowerShell scripts to automate tasks such as creating/terminating users, updating groups/licenses, updating Group Policy, rebuilding mail profiles, and exports.
 - Configured Microsoft SSO for Zoom, Webex, Paycor, and more cloud applications.
- **Virtualization** Facilitated migration from on-premise exchange server to Microsoft Exchange Online. Moving the on-premise file server to OneDrive is in progress.
 - Transitioned company of 400 employees from Office 2016 to Office 365 Suite utilizing Office Deployment Tool. Modified .xml to better suit company ever-shifting needs.
 - Led team in all aspects of migration from Cisco Unified Connection Manager to Cisco Webex with the Webex Contact Center
- **Networking** Creates and modifies DHCP reservations for security cameras, printers, servers, wireless access points. Makes Firewall changes for disaster recovery. Utilizes Putty to manage ports, such as changing vlans and shut/no shut ports
- Management Monitored network devices to diagnose/resolve hardware and software issues promptly, as well as, identify
 where upgrades would be most beneficial. Utilized Maas360 for Company iPhone management and compliance.

Compass MSP | West Hartford, CT Escalation Technician III | 03/2022 - 09/2022

- **Versatile** Managed everyday tasks for over 300 local companies varying network environments. Creating/terminating users, managing group policy, software installs, network/software troubleshooting, and much more across companies utilizing On-Premise, Azure, AWS, and GCP.
- Customer Satisfaction Served as a Third Tier Escalation technician to apply critical thinking and research to address
 complex network/software issues. Consulted end users to ask probing questions to locate root causes. Maintained
 quality assurance and customer satisfaction objectives. Inspected equipment operation to diagnose and troubleshoot
 reported issues.
- **Security** Weekly on-site to a Secret facility to manage every aspect of the company. From verifying compliance and audit security to creating Linux VMs, each visit was a different task.

Commence Fitness | Southington, CT Personal Trainer | 07/2021 - 03/2022

- **Trustworthy** Built trust and rapport with clients to determine goals and optimize them achieving those goals.
- Dedicated Studied multiple programs to provide health education, wellness and fitness program development to clients. -Wrote custom tailored programs and meal plans for clients to follow.

United States Navy, USN

Information Systems Technician | 05/2017 - 05/2021

• **Eager to Leam** - Started off my career provisioning Windows/Linux workstations and creating user accounts/groups. - After demonstrating proficiency, graduated to managing distros/security groups to access shared files and creating Windows and Linux VMs.

Diverse - Performed maintenance on Top Secret, Secret, Confidential, and Unclassified networks.
 Learned how to manage/implement Group Policy and SQL databases. - Performed monthly network reboots and baremetal restores to practice disaster recovery. - As Command Fiber Technician, identified issues and rebuilt network connectivity.

Skills

Motivated, Adaptable, Detail-Oriented, Time-Management, Active Directory, Group Policy, Disaster Recovery, DNS/DHCP, PowerShell, Putty, Python, Virtualization, Automation, Troubleshooting/Debugging, Windows/MacOS/Linux, Azure/AWS/GCP

Education

Southington High School High School Diploma | 06/2016

Certificates

Microsoft Azure Associate (AZ-104), Microsoft Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)